Guide to the Charles M. Stein Papers SC1224
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers
  - Statistics 116, 1976 Winter (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - The Nation magazine, 2004 Jul 19-26 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - sufficient statistics binder contents, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - on a Nec. And Suff. Admissibility of estimators when strictly convex, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Statistics 2nd year examination, 1974 May 4 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Technical report, 1971 Feb 12 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Large sample theory Statistics 332a, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - 5. balanced incomplete block designs (BIED), undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Hoadley, 1970 Mar (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - 2nd research report Matsubara, 1970 Nov 6 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - lecture 5 dual systems, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - technical report estimation of the mean, 1973 Jun 23 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - probability chapter II sections chapter III, undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - I. Introductory Chapter notes on statistical decision theory, 1969 Jun (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Convex functions, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Probability Chapter 1, Sections 10-13, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Probability (first version) Chapter I, Sections 1-6, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Analysis of Variance, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - D.O.D sponsored research at Stanford Volume 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - linear spaces, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - On Lp Chebyshev-Cramer Asymptotic Expansions, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - decision theory, rough, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Applications of Convex function probability chapter 4 Sections 1-6, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Normal approximation, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - The Admissibility of Pitman's estimator for two location parameters technical report, 1959 Feb 6 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Berkeley lecture second version, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Statistical decision theory binder contents, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The determination of single sampling attribute plans with given producer's and consumer's risk, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - II. Statistical preliminaries, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Estimation, 1963 Jun (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - III. Least squares, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Multiple regression and Estimation of the mean … Baranchik, 1964 Apr (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Lecture notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - lecture notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - lecture notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - prime number theory, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - concentration inequalities with exchangeable pairs, 2005 Jun (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Binder contents, 2002 Jul (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Sequential design, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - lecture notes in binder, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - preliminary course preparation, 2003 Sep (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Poisson approximation, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - some problems in multivariate analysis by Stein, 1956 Oct 25 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - unlabeled, 2000 Nov (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Jordan canonical form, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - new poisson binomial, 1997 Oct 31 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - correspondence from Makoto Aoshima, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 53rd session of International Statistical Institute, 2001 Aug 22-29 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - unlabeled, 2000 Mar 1 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Technical Report Flexible Descriminant, 1997 Mar (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Classification by Pairwise Coupling Technical Report, 1997 Feb (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Metrics and Models technical report, 1997 Mar (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Arratia Independence of Prime Factors, 1997 Apr 29 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - What do we know about the Metropolis Algorithm? Technical Report, 1995 Apr (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Iterates of expanding maps, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Compound Poisson approximations, 1997 Aug 18 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - An example for Stein's method, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Compound Poisson and Poisson process approximations, 1997 Jul 2 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Stein's method and the Zero Bias Transformation, 1997 May 3 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Stein's method and the Zero Bias Transformation, 1997 Aug 15 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Reinert, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Poisson process approximation for sequence repeats, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Multivariate analysis I technical report, 1969 Dec 2 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Reinert papers, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Geometry of the space of phylogenetic trees, 2000 May (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - The Nation newspaper, 2010 Nov 15 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Progress in Stein's method, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Statistics of biological network motifs, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Goldstein Bounds on the Constant in the Mean Central Limit Theorem, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - unlabeled, 1995 Aug 5 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - on Errors in the variables Zellner, Sankar, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Technical Report stephens, Dodge, 1967 Mar (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - lecture notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Invoices/reciepts, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - University of Washington, 1985 Sep (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Department of Mathematics, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - University correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - math notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - magazines, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Global exchange, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Central limit theory, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New York Times newspaper, 1994 Sep 22 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Chen paper rate of convergence, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Barbour, holst paper, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Technical report no. 42, 1969 Dec 12 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Wald lectures summary, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - lecture notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Some applications of Chen-Stein, 1988 Mar (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - math notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - outline of lecture, notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Poisson approximation, 1993 Jul 19 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Nationality Issues, 1990 Mar 22 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - reprints, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - reprints, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - reprints, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Lectures on sequential analysis, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Lectures on sequential analysis (second version), undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Lectures on sequential analysis, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - students, t, etc., undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Decision theory: Summary of Group Theory, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Lectures on sequential analysis (third version), undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sequential analysis II, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Hotellings T2 - Test, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Topics in Statistical Decision Theory, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Decision Theory: Summary of Theory of Zero-Sum Two-Person Games, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - A central limit theorem, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Summary of Wald Lectures, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - unlabeled typescript, undated (Box 31)
  - Introduction to Random Permutations, 1992 Jul (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - TV, 1992 Oct 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Part of Lecture 1 Exchangeable pairs Lecture 5: the basic diagram, Lecture 4: The Kernel of E. normal tools, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - VI, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - III contents, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Urn problems sums, 1992 Jun 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Further work on NA302 normal approximation for sums of IDD breal random variables, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Stein, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - miscellaneous, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - unlabeled, 1993 Sep (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Charts, papers, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Handwritten notes, postcards, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Notebooks
  - Notebooks (Box 1-9)
  - Notebooks (Box 15-16)
  - Notebooks (Box 19-20)
  - Notebooks (Box 22)
  - Notebooks (Box 24)
  - Notebooks (Box 26)
  - Notebooks (Box 28)
  - Notebooks (Box 34)
- Computer Media
  - Computer disks (zip and floppy 3.5) (Box 32)